{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "quiz_title": "TEST 1 QUIZ 3",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "Which of the following is true about multiplexing?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Multiplexing is a form of modulation done at the transmitter side to convert analog signals to digital signals.",
            "b. Space division multiplexing allows multiple input sources to be carried via the same medium but not at the same time.",
            "c. In FDM, signals from multiple sources are interleaved by bits, bytes, or frames.",
            "d. Statistical TDM allows prioritization of channels by assigning different numbers of time slots for each input."
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. Statistical TDM allows prioritization of channels by assigning different numbers of time slots for each input."
        },
        {
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "Which of the following is true about CDM?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Each user is assigned a pseudo-random code, which should be orthogonal to all the other codes.",
            "b. The receiver has prior knowledge of the orthogonal code.",
            "c. The orthogonal code spreads the signal such that the resulting signal will have higher bandwidth.",
            "d. All of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. All of the choices"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "Packet Switching is a method that transmits digital information which are cut into smaller pieces of information that may take different routes.",
          "choices": [
            "Packet switching"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "Packet switching"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "________ Approach is a packet switching approach wherein each packet takes different routes and is routed depending on the identifiers in the packet.",
          "choices": [
            "Datagram"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "Datagram"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "In circuit switching, ________ is a method wherein paths are separated spatially and requires interconnection in a grid to complete the end-to-end physical link.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Crossbar switch",
            "b. TSI incorrect",
            "c. TDM bus",
            "d. None of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "a. Crossbar switch"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 6,
          "question": "In circuit switching, ________ is a method wherein a path between an output and input is managed by a control unit depending on the allotted time slot.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Crossbar switch",
            "b. TSI incorrect",
            "c. TDM bus",
            "d. None of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. TDM bus"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 7,
          "question": "Which of the following is part of the X.25 packet header?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Error detecting code",
            "b. Data",
            "c. Logical channel number",
            "d. All of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. All of the choices"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 8,
          "question": "Which of the following is part of the X.25 packet header?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Address field",
            "b. Packet identifier",
            "c. Logical channel number",
            "d. All of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. Logical channel number"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 9,
          "question": "Which of the following is an example of a copper-guided transmission medium?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Waveguide",
            "b Coaxial cable",
            "c. Fiber optic cable",
            "d. All of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b Coaxial cable"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 10,
          "question": "Which of the following is used to transmit electrical signals?",
          "choices": [
            "a Coaxial cable",
            "b. Fiber optic cable",
            "c. Waveguide",
            "d. All of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "a Coaxial cable"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 11,
          "question": "Which of the following is used to transmit radio waves?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Coaxial cable",
            "b. Fiber optic cable",
            "c. Waveguide",
            "d. None of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. Waveguide"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 12,
          "question": "Which of the cables was used for 10Base2 Ethernet?",
          "choices": [
            "a. RG59",
            "b. RG58",
            "c. RG11",
            "d. RJ45"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b. RG58"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 13,
          "question": "Which of the cables was used for 10Base5 Ethernet?",
          "choices": [
            "a. RG59",
            "b. RG58",
            "c. RG11",
            "d. RJ45"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. RG11"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 14,
          "question": "________ is a type of fiber optic cable that has a uniform core refractive index and where light waves often travel in a single path.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Multimode step index",
            "b. Single-mode step index",
            "c. Multimode graded index",
            "d. Single multimode graded index"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b. Single-mode step index"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 15,
          "question": "In fiber optic cables, the density of the core is highest at the center and lowest at the edge (near the cladding).",
          "choices": [
            "a. Multimode step index",
            "b. Single-mode step index",
            "c. Multimode graded index",
            "d. Single multimode graded index"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. Multimode graded index"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 16,
          "question": "________ is commonly used for AM broadcasting.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Surface wave propagation",
            "b. Sky wave propagation",
            "c. Space wave propagation",
            "d. Satellite propagation"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "a. Surface wave propagation"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 17,
          "question": "________ uses highly directional antennas so that the signal travels in a straight line from one point to another in the Earth's surface.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Surface wave propagation",
            "b. Sky wave propagation",
            "c. Space wave propagation",
            "d. Satellite propagation"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. Space wave propagation"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 18,
          "question": "________ is also known as ionospheric propagation.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Surface wave propagation",
            "b. Sky wave propagation",
            "c. Space wave propagation",
            "d. Satellite propagation"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b. Sky wave propagation"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 19,
          "question": "How many voice channels does T1 line carry?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 24",
            "b. 48",
            "c. 96",
            "d. 192"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "a. 24"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 20,
          "question": "How many voice channels does T2 line carry?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 24",
            "b. 48",
            "c. 96",
            "d. 192"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. 96"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 21,
          "question": "How many voice channels does T3 line carry?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 96",
            "b. 192",
            "c. 384",
            "d 672"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d 672"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 22,
          "question": "How many voice channels does T5 line carry?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 1024",
            "b. 2048",
            "c. 4032",
            "d 8064"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d 8064"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 23,
          "question": "How many T1 lines can a T3 line carry?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 12",
            "b. 24",
            "c. 28",
            "d. 48"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. 28"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 24,
          "question": "What is the line speed of T1 line in Mbps?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 1.544 Mbps",
            "b. 2.048 Mbps",
            "c. 3.152 Mbps",
            "d. 6.312 Mbps"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "a. 1.544 Mbps"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 25,
          "question": "What is the line speed of E3 line in Mbps?",
          "choices": [
            "a. 0.064 Mbps",
            "b. 2.048 Mbps",
            "c. 8.448 Mbps",
            "d 34.368 Mbps"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d 34.368 Mbps"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quiz_title": "TEST 2 QUIZ 4",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "A nonprofit US trade association that establishes and recommends industrial standards.",
          "choices": [
            "a. IEEE",
            "b. EIA",
            "c. TIA",
            "d. ISO"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b. EIA"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "A standards organization responsible for the 802.xx series standards.",
          "choices": [
            "a. IEEE",
            "b. EIA",
            "c. TIA",
            "d. ISO"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "a. IEEE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "ANSI is the official standards agency of the US (acronym).",
          "choices": [
            "American National Standards Institute"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "American National Standards Institute"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "ETSI is the European Standards Organization dealing with telecommunications, broadcasting, and other communication services (acronym).",
          "choices": [
            "European Telecommunications Standards Institute"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "European Telecommunications Standards Institute"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "IETF is a technical advisory group of the Internet Society that oversees the architecture and procedures used in the Internet.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "FALSE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 6,
          "question": "RFC are documents maintained by IETF containing information about Internet Protocols (acronym).",
          "choices": [
            "Request for Comments"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "Request for Comments"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 7,
          "question": "An organization that promotes long-term research of importance to the evolution of the future Internet.",
          "choices": [
            "a. IETF",
            "b. IRTF (Internet Research Task Force)",
            "c. IAB",
            "d. IEEE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b. IRTF (Internet Research Task Force)"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 8,
          "question": "It is a non-treaty organization whose membership is comprised mainly of standards organizations of various countries and is responsible for Open Systems Interconnect (OSI) model.",
          "choices": [
            "a. IEEE",
            "b. IETF",
            "c. ITU",
            "d. ISO"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. ISO"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 9,
          "question": "It is the United Nations specialized agency for information and communication technologies (ICTs).",
          "choices": [
            "a. IEEE",
            "b. IETF",
            "c. ITU",
            "d. ISO"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. ITU"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 10,
          "question": "An ITU series of standards that cover the global information infrastructure, Internet protocol aspects, next generation networks, Internet of Things, and smart cities.",
          "choices": [
            "a. W",
            "b. X",
            "c. Y",
            "d. Z"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. Y"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 11,
          "question": "IEEE 802.15.1 is the equivalent standard for Bluetooth.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "TRUE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 12,
          "question": "Which of the following is a PAN?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Wi-Fi",
            "b Zigbee",
            "c. 1G",
            "d. 2G"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b Zigbee"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 13,
          "question": "A class 3 bluetooth can reach a distance of 100 meters.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "FALSE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 14,
          "question": "Bluetooth Low Energy is also known as Wibro.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "FALSE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 15,
          "question": "The standard for Zigbee is",
          "choices": [
            "a. IEEE 802.3",
            "b. IEEE 805.11",
            "c. IEEE 802.15.2",
            "d. IEEE 805.15.4"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. IEEE 805.15.4"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 16,
          "question": "Advanced Mobile Telephone Systems (AMTS) was used in the 1st generation of Mobile Network Technologies",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "FALSE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 17,
          "question": "The main drawback of the 1G Mobile Network Technologies is interoperability with different countries.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "TRUE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 18,
          "question": "A Mobile Network technology that uses TDMA to multiplex up to 8 calls per channel in the 900 and 1800 MHz bands.",
          "choices": [
            "a. AMTS",
            "b. TACS",
            "c. CDMA",
            "d. GSM"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. GSM"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 19,
          "question": "It enables cellular network operators to provide Internet access, instant messaging, and multimedia messaging using second-generation Mobile Networks.",
          "choices": [
            "a. TACS",
            "b. AMTS",
            "c. GPRS",
            "d. FHSS"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. GPRS"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 20,
          "question": "HSDPA is a 3G packet-based data service in WCDMA downlink with data transmission up to 8-10 Mbit/s over a 5 MHz bandwidth in WCDMA downlink.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "TRUE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 21,
          "question": "4G uses network wide based IP-based packet switching.",
          "choices": [
            "TRUE",
            "FALSE"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "TRUE"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 22,
          "question": "________ is a type of malware that takes control over a device without user knowledge.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Virus",
            "b. Trojan horse",
            "c. Worm",
            "d. Man-in-the-middle"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "b. Trojan horse"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 23,
          "question": "________ is a technique to improve a malicious website's ranking through increasing traffic to the malicious website.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Phishing",
            "b. Vulnerability exploitation",
            "c. DDoS",
            "d. SEO poisoning"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. SEO poisoning"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 24,
          "question": "Which of the following is a good practice to protect devices and networks?",
          "choices": [
            "a. Use antivirus and antispyware",
            "b. Keep firewall on",
            "c. Update OS",
            "d. All of the choices"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "d. All of the choices"
        },
        {
          "question_number": 25,
          "question": "________ is a type of firewall that hides private addresses of hosts in a local area network.",
          "choices": [
            "a. Host-based firewall",
            "b. Proxy server",
            "c. NAT firewall",
            "d. Network layer firewall"
          ],
          "correct_answer": "c. NAT firewall"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}